Master Fitz, not at me.
I've been at the University of Magic for about a year.
Enough time for me to turn 16.
I still begin each day with a workout.
Only new thing about that is some added motivation.
I never know how to talk to this guy.
Still kind of scared of him.
Tell me.
Yeah?
Why do you desire strength?
I'm not quite sure how to answer that.
I've known many men obsessed with the pursuit of strength, fame, and fortune.
Not a decent one among them, if you ask me.
All narrow-minded.
There are more worthwhile things to chase in life.
Like what, would you say?
Like women, boy!
You'll understand once you find one yourself.
Speaking of, Your Majesty.
What is it?
Do you happen to know a cure for impotence?
I do not.
Hmm.
After a little training, it's time for breakfast, and then on to class.
What a pain in the ass.
You're telling me, duh.
Can you believe this weather?
It's just lovely.
Since that duel with Badi Gadi, most of the other students steer clear of me.
Come on, you can cut Goliad a little bit of slack, boss.
Her heart's in the right place and everything.
Besides, I'd like it if you tried to make us look good in front of the other beast folk, Meow.
With all the minions that you have at this point, it's gotten tougher being your number two.
Hey, Meow, I'm the boss's number two!
Now, now, there's no need to argue about it, okay?
I consider you both my number two.
Way to miss the point, boss.
We need a clearly defined hierarchy.
Yes, we do.
Like, since you can beat Silent Fits, you can basically run this place.
Me in charge here?
No, thank you.
Now grow a pair and show off your claws, Meow!
Not happening.
Hmm.
Brutus.
What all do you know about curses?
A growing interest of his lately.
Curses, huh?
Curses.
A friend once told me that Laplace transferred his curse to objects,
and that let him force the curse onto others.
That's so.
Hmm?
He cursed the spears he gave the Superd in the Laplace War.
They didn't use their own.
And basically, it caused them to go on a bloody rampage, which led to their whole race being vilified.
Seriously?
That's how that started?
Oh.
Uh.
Sounds like.
Just according to what I heard, at least.
Fascinating.
Transferring a curse.
That's very helpful.
Thanks, Rudeus.
I've got an idea on what to do now.
After class, it's lunchtime.
How about we grab a seat right here?
Good idea, as Julie wouldn't be able to join us on the third floor.
Hey, that's Rudeus.
Guy's a powerhouse.
Took down every other special student in his first year.
Oh, yeah.
Not to mention one-shotting the Demon King in front of literally everybody.
I don't mind getting my ego stroked, of course.
But I can't let it go to my head.
If it isn't my mighty little friend, all tucked away in a corner.
Master, that thing His Majesty's drinking looks so yummy.
Spoken like a true dwarf.
Incredible that she can discern quality at such a young age.
Yes.
You wouldn't be opposed to sharing a drop or two with us, Your Majesty.
Surely you jest, boy.
Few things are less fun than drinking alone.
But don't stop at a drop.
Guzzle away!
Yes.
This is not a beverage to be sipped.
Then maybe it'd be better to wait until after class.
That's your wish.
I shall obey.
It's a tough road for you scholars, huh?
After lunch, I retreat to this lab covered in magic-resistant brick for summoning experiments.
My part in this isn't too demanding.
I just pour mana into magic circles that Nanahoshi devised herself.
They say most proven summoning circles have been lost.
But by studying the principles behind them, coupled with lots of experimentation with countless different circles,
she's managed to invent a few of her own original spells.
Gotta say, I'm very impressed.
Was that a success?
Nope.
Another dead.
Now, with me here, she's taking the kitchen sink approach.
We're testing more circles than I can count.
So, hey, what is the end goal of this experiment, exactly?
Eventually, I want to summon a person from our world.
But in the short term, I'm just trying to work out the major principles on a much smaller scale.
It shouldn't be possible.
But if she can draw a circle that summons a person, she should be able to draw one that sends them back as well.
That's the hope, anyway.
Let me ask you something.
Say you do make that happen.
Besides getting home, won't that cause another big mana disaster?
I'm planning to avoid that, of course.
If I can prove a few more theorems, I can form a hypothesis as to why it happened in the first place,
and how to keep it from happening again.
Well, they say that failure is part of experimentation, so please don't take the risk too lightly, okay?
Obviously.
Why do you think I'm starting with the basics?
You know, I would love to learn about summoning magic myself.
You must understand, this knowledge is my lifeline.
I need to be careful about sharing it.
Yeah, but part of this arrangement was that you would share it.
Okay, fine. I'll tell you one thing after this experiment, promise.
Only one? Doesn't seem worth it to me.
Well, think of it this way. As soon as my research is done and I've gone home, you get access to all my writing.
I'm sure you can be patient in the meantime.
I guess begging before we actually get anything done would be pretty pathetic.
If you want to know that badly, do some research of your own.
Thanks, I appreciate it.
After dinner, I give Julie magic lessons.
And then on to figure making. This is still Julie's first year, so her mana capacity is fairly low and I wouldn't say she has much finesse.
I mean, she is good with her hands. But she's only just started using sculpting tools so her skills aren't honed yet.
Look at this side of the face.
We've got to think in the long term.
Since I met Nana Hoshi, I haven't been to the library nearly as much.
And that's how my days go by.
Still no lead on a cure though.
I haven't seen much of Master Fitz lately either.
Then one day I received a letter.
It says it's from Soldot.
Soldot Heckler. Head honcho of Step Leader. Blast from the past.
Okay, so he's in Sharia for a big guild meetup and he wants to grab a bite to eat for old times sake. Catch up a bit.
I wonder if this is what it feels like to reconnect with your old high school buddies or something.
Gotta say, it ain't bad.
How you doing, Quagmire? I haven't seen you in ages, man.
Yeah, it almost feels like a whole lifetime ago.
You gotta get rid of the baby clothes. You look like a run-of-the-mill rookie in that get-up.
Maybe I miss those days and I want to go back. Give me your bag. Let me carry it somewhere.
You carrying our bags? Are you nuts? We ought to be carrying yours.
You did after that stray dragon fight. We're good.
Man, we made out like bandits on that one.
Anyway, what's up with you, Alphiers?
What's a mega-slut like you doing with a boyfriend? Is this a joke or something?
No, merely proof that no man I've ever met has truly won my heart before.
But now, I found the man of my dreams and I couldn't be happier.
You may find it hard to believe, but I can be quite devoted.
No way that's how they met.
Hey, Sol. Inter-party meeting.
Another? Are you kidding me? We talked all morning, didn't we?
What do you expect? The whole clan's fired up. Might as well get it out of the way.
And here I thought I would kind of enjoy myself this afternoon.
Sorry, Quagmire. I gotta run. But let's do this again, alright?
Yeah. Just let me know when you're in town.
So, what now? You two have anything planned for the rest of the day?
Not really, no. But actually, we were talking about giving Cliff a crash course in adventuring.
If you would care to join us?
Uh... You needn't come. I don't intend to rely on your help.
In that case, I'll just head on back to school.
Then do take care going back and please give everyone our best.
And I know you know this, but please remember that you have a beginner with you,
so don't go anywhere too dangerous. Cool?
Sure thing.
Excuse me?
Yes, Rudeus, we'll be careful. No challenging dragons or demon kings.
Hey.
Should the two of them be out here? Who's guarding the princess?
Well, I better at least say hi.
Hey, you two. Fancy meeting you all the way out here.
Who do you... Oh great, it's you.
Sounds like he still doesn't like me very much. But as long as I can stay friends with Master Fitz, who cares.
What's up? You okay, Master Fitz? There's something different about you today.
I can't put my finger on it. The way he carries himself.
What do you need? Speak your piece and move along, would you?
Did I catch them at a bad time?
Don't tell me. Are they on a date?
Are they on a date?
Yeah, maybe Luke swings both ways, and he and Fitz have a sparring practice.
I just happened to see you, so I thought I would say hello.
Um, Master Fitz?
I see. We appreciate the greeting. I have to remind you, however, that Fitz isn't permitted to speak while guarding Her Highness. Apologies. I'm sure you understand.
I guess I really did come at a bad time. Still, it seems harsh for him to ignore me completely like this.
What is it?
Oh, it's nothing. Um, excuse me.
I don't think I'd let anything show on the outside, but man, that really stung.
Why would he shun me like that? It hurts so much I can hardly even think straight.
I've been mulling it over, but I still can't figure out why Master Fitz was avoiding me just now.
I don't remember doing anything to offend him. I just want to talk about my feelings with someone. Well, no, I just want to gripe. I'm pretty sure Xanobah is at the Mages Guild right now for some blessed child research.
He probably took Julie with him. Now, Linia and Persina would be terrible listeners. Probably make fun of me. And Nanahoshi kind of has her hands full. She won't want to listen to my problems.
Okay, whatever. Might as well go to the library.
Might as well go to the library.
Oh, hey.
Hey, Rudeus. Been a little while, hasn't it?
He's just his normal self.
Is there a problem? Do I have something on my face?
Why did you ignore me in the market earlier today?
I'm sorry, but it really is true that I'm not allowed to speak while I'm on duty, you know? Silent fits.
People don't take me seriously because of my voice. It's childish. So in public, I'm not supposed to speak, especially around Princess Ariel.
Okay, but I didn't see the princess anywhere around you.
She was in a shop nearby. We aren't her only protection.
Forgive me for demanding your attention, then. Poor timing, I guess.
Mm-mm. It's alright. I feel bad that I couldn't respond to you, though.
Okay, I think I see what's happening here.
I'm not positive, but I think Princess Ariel has actually been disguising herself as Master Fitz somehow.
So she was trying to avoid me earlier because any careless chitchat could blow her cover.
The more I think about it, the more sense it makes overall.
But either way, there's still no evidence that Fitz is mad at me. And that's all I really care about. So, good.
Well, that's a relief. I was starting to worry that you suddenly started hating me or something.
No, of course not. How could I ever hate you?
Every little thing he does sticks with me. The way he scratches behind his ears. The way he stretches when he finishes a study session. The way he smells when he brushes close by me.
And then there's that smile. I can't get that bashful smile out of my head.
I know what all this means, of course.
I'm in love.
I'm in love with a man. Assuming he really is one, which... Hmm.
Professor Genus?
Well, hello, Rudeus. What brings you to see me today?
Well, I want to ask about Master Fitz.
Then you'll have to forgive me. The staff have been given rather strict instructions regarding him and his employer.
I see, of course. Could you confirm basic information for me, like his sex?
Like his sex? Well, yes. Hmm.
Silent Fitz, Ismael.
Well, that was pretty unconvincing. And what was that about Suzy?
What was that about Suzy?
Ismael?
Well, that was pretty unconvincing. And what was that about strict instruction regarding Fitz?
What would I do if he actually turned out to be a woman? Would I ask him out?
Wish I could at least jerk off about it.
Oh.
What did you say?
I... I'm so sorry.
Oh.
I'm so sorry.
No, you're mistaken! I... I'm a man!
Master Fitz is a woman. That's a big deal. But even more importantly...
I got a boner. Amazing!
I can't believe it. All because I came to investigate the Mana Disaster. Thank you, Lord Mangod.
Although, Fitz obviously wants to be known as a man.
Well, fine. He... she... has done so much for me. I can't betray that.
I have a responsibility to respect her wishes and help her keep up the act for however long she wants.
Master Fitz definitely holds the key to curing my ED. But I can't get any more intimate with him now. Maybe soon.
Hey.
I guess this cure still has a long way to go. Oh well. I can see my way forward. So why rush?
Master Fitz.
To be sure!
trouble
La-ya-la-ya-la